ARTON RAMADANI

Web Developer

EMAIL: artonramadani25@gmail.com

ADDRESS: STR. REXHEP KRASNIQI 376-1, PRISHTINA

PHONE: +38345944338

DATE OF BIRTH: 09-25-1999

NATIONALITY: ALBANIAN



OBJECTIVE

Proactive, oriented to fulfill the tasks that are my responsibility and most importantly to finish them in time. Received excellent feedback from professors and employees during my studies on my ability to work with team members and on my ability to learn whilst at once developing team projects.

EXPERIENCE

Prishtine

January 2021 – April 2021

Front/Back-end Developer

Kapaku Web

During the time that I worked at KapakuWeb I successfully programed web pages using different technologies like html5, CSS, javascript, php, MySQL, Wordpress etc. During this time I have worked here, I learned the ethics of work and the and the know the responsibility's that every worker need's to have in certain projects assigned to them.

Shtime

January 2020 – February 2020

FREELANCER

NNP "Agroni"

Successfully programmed an application that will help the owner better manage his income and outcomes, his workers, and the working tools that the owner has.

Shtime 2013-2017

4 YEARS SCHOOLS' CABINET MAINTENANCE

Gymnasium "Naim Frasheri" - Shtime 3 years

Elementary school "Hasan Prishtina" – Godanc 1 year

During my studies I have successfully repaired more than 50 computers, and maintained them by updating and in some cases fixing hardware and software. While having this responsibility which I have been awarded with certificates, I also held extra classes with students who felt that they needed extra hours of study in the field of technology.

EDUCATION AND

TRAINING

Computer Science and Engineering

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering, University for Business

and Technology, Prishtina November 2021

Successfully graduated from UBT majoring CSE where I learned different technology's to develop different applications, whether they are web based

(html, css, JavaScript,php) or local apps(Java, SQL). Learned to design projects using different architectures and methodology's such as MVC, microservices, Monolith Architectures etc. (Relative gained knowledge: virtual machines, networking, phases of project development, project presentation etc.)

Youth Career IT Pathway- YCIP

Certified by the **American university of Kosova** for successfully finishing the training Youth Career IT Pathway (YCIP), Prishtina December 2019

Konrad-Adenauer-Stiftung awards

Successfully finished the training for **'The role of youth in modern campaigning"**, founded by Konrad Adenauer Stiftung 24-26 February 2017 Prevalle, Kosove

Gymnasium of Science, Shtime, Kosove June 2017

Other certificates:

"TOEFL test classes-Test of English as a Foreign Language", March 2016,

"SAT test classes, Test of writing, critical thinking and mathematics", March 2016

"English Language School LindaStar", Ferizaj, Kosove June 2010 – September 2014

SKILLS

- Networking
- VMware
- Data Security
- Database
- Data Recovery
- Adobe Photoshop
- Front End Developer
- Fast Learner
- Self-motivated
- Can work with Windows, MacOS and Linux

LANGUAGES

Mother tongue(s): Albanian

Other language(s):

	Understanding:		Speaking:		Writing:
	Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	
			English	production	
English:	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
	English Certificates. Advanced				
	Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user – B1 and B2: Independent user – C1 and				
	C2: Proficient user				